<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on sean&#39;s archives</title>
    <link>https://example.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on sean&#39;s archives</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 13:34:29 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Therapy</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/therapy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 13:34:29 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/therapy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;im-starting-therapy&#34;&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m starting therapy&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After a conversation with my psychiatrist, it was concluded that I needed a nAch/TAT exam to have my motivation, energy, and short-term goals and prospects analyzed in order to aid theraputic processes to help my college journey. I have to admit, it sounds like a big step, but I&amp;rsquo;m all up for it anyway. Looking back at how I &amp;ldquo;fumbled&amp;rdquo; senior high school, this was my only hope of surviving college and my future programming career.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life Update</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/life-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 21:05:04 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/life-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;stuff-can-be-tiring-yet-rewarding&#34;&gt;Stuff can be tiring yet rewarding&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some weeks ago, kuya Jay approached me on my plans regarding college and my career. Said I wasn&amp;rsquo;t prepared yet for college so I was planning to get a job first to get decent gear. Like a lot of people that really wanted to get a job too, I&amp;rsquo;m very excited. The thought of saving up for new stuff I can use really is exciting and I want to commit to it. One thing he said to me was to value what I already have and still planning to even take further, education. &amp;ldquo;People will not respect you unless you have a diploma,&amp;rdquo; and boy did it hit me hard. I reassessed myself on what my capabilities are and how I see school, not just because of my worry to be respected, like how a human should act, but on how this will affect my future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
